frugalfun4boys.com 2019-07-09

# Disclosure and Privacy Policy - Frugal Fun For Boys and Girls

**This privacy policy was updated May 22, 2018.**

Here at Frugal Fun for Boys and Girls, we value your privacy while online.  This policy explains how and why your data is collected and stored while visiting this site.

**Frugal Fun for Boys and Girls** is a website written and edited by Sarah Dees, with creative input from the kids as well.  We share learning activities, crafts, STEM projects, original designs with LEGO® bricks, and more. This website was created in 2010, and we are based in Texas.

By using this website, you are agreeing to be bound by this privacy policy.

**Here is how your information will be collected on this site:**

  * If you leave a comment
  * If you subscribe to the weekly newsletter
  * Through website cookies
  * Through Google Analytics

**Newsletter**

If you sign up for the newsletter using either the box in the sidebar or the banner at the top of the site, you’ll be asked to enter your email address.  This is because… well, it would be hard to send you an email without your address!

I send newsletter emails once a week, and occasionally I send special activity emails or holiday emails with crafts and activities that fit the current holiday.  I may also send emails about special deals or promotions that will fit your interests.  At the bottom of every newsletter there is a button to unsubscribe. You can unsubscribe at any time.  If you are having trouble unsubscribing, feel free to email me at frugalfun4boys@gmail.com.

I currently use MadMimi as my email provider.  They store your data but never sell or transfer your email address.  Your clicks within the newsletter are stored to allow me to see what’s popular and what’s not so that I can create future newsletters that suit my readers’ needs.  You can [read MadMimi’s privacy policy here](https://uk.godaddy.com/Agreements/Privacy.aspx).

**Comments**

I love hearing from my readers! To make a comment, you may leave it anonymously or leave a name, email address, website, and comment.  It’s not a good idea to leave a comment with personal information on any site, so I highly recommend that you don’t do that!

Your information is collected to identify you as the commenter, but it is not given away or sold.  Only your name and comment are displayed on the site.  Your information will remain in the site database unless we delete it or the post is deleted.

**Google Analytics**

Like most websites around the world, I use Google Analytics to see which posts my readers are visiting. It helps me discern what content is the most popular and helpful to readers.  Google Analytics collects information about your location down to the town level, the type of device you are using (tablet, desktop, mobile) and the browser you are using.  None of this information can be used to identify you, and I wouldn’t want to anyway.  It just helps me to see traffic patterns.  You can [read more about how user data is retained here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=en&utm_id=ad).

**Advertisements**

We use third party advertisements on this site to support the site and keep the content free of charge for you.

Ads are run on this site by AdThrive.

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Texas real estate ads to someone in Texas, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**Cookies**

Nope, not the cookies you eat!

This website uses a technology called “cookies” and server logs to collect information about how the site is used. Cookies are little pieces of code that I use to track your use of this site and provide the best possible experience for you.

Cookies may collect information including the date and time of your visit, the pages viewed, time spent on the site, and your IP address.

If you want to disable cookies, you can do so through the settings on your web browser (Chrome, Firefox, Safari, etc.).

**Amazon Affiliate Program**

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.  Links to Amazon in my posts are affiliate links, which means that if you buy something through a link, I will earn a small percentage of the sale at no additional cost to you.

If you would like your information to be removed from our systems, please email me at frugalfun4boys@gmail.com
